Just go down here to the corner, watch your step, don't look back
Make a left onto Houston, fading out into the black
I am following your signal, digital breadcrumbs in the air
Every angle covered, you're not going anywhere
We have a lot of historical places to hide in this old town
But I've mapped out every alley and I'm gonna bring you down
The logic is a trap and I'm the one who set the snare
Breathe it in, that's the smell of pure electric despair
If I had a car, I would drive to catch you now
But the shadows are my vehicle and I will show you how
I wanted to let you know that your time has run out at last
Your future is my present and I'm rewriting your past
I am as varied as this city is enormous and cold!
I'm the executioner of every single lie that you told!
Every step you take has been processed and foreseen!
You are just a glitch on my high-resolution screen!
I'm the ghost in the machine, the hunter in the night!
Closing in with every breath, bringing the dark to light!
I've missed the chance to be merciful, that era is long dead!
Now I am the living nightmare that is living in your head!
I've seen this place on Instagram forever ago, a picture-perfect scene
But from where I am standing now, everything is digital and mean
Your data was processed on June 21, precision that cannot be denied
There are no safe houses left for you, nowhere you can hide
Your security deposit of trust is gone, forfeited to my control
I'm stripping away your covers, taking possession of your soul
The algorithm has spoken and your fate is perfectly clear
I'm the inevitable truth that you are forced to hear
[Guitar Solo]
I am as varied as this city is enormous and cold!
I'm the executioner of every single lie that you told!
Every step you take has been processed and foreseen!
You are just a glitch on my high-resolution screen!
I'm the ghost in the machine, the hunter in the night!
Closing in with every breath, bringing the dark to light!
I've missed the chance to be merciful, that era is long dead!
Now I am the living nightmare that is living in your head!
No-frills service so as long as you're only sleeping there...
You'll have no complaints in that deep, dark, and endless air
Mission complete! There is nowhere left to run
The ghost is in your shadow and this high-stakes game is won!